frightcatalog.com 2011-11-15

# Privacy Policy

Policy as of 11/15/2011

## PRIVACY STATEMENT

FrightCatalog.com values its customer and respects their privacy. Any time you visit a website on the Internet, your computer exchanges information with other computers. FrightCatalog.com recognizes that it must maintain and use customer information responsibly. This privacy policy explains what personal information is collected through this web site, how that information is used, and how it is kept safe. This policy only applies to FrightCatalog.com and no other web site. If you ever have a question about this policy or information that it shared with FrightCatalog.com, please email us at [service@frightcatalog.com](mailto:service@frightcatalog.com) or fill out our online contact form.

## PERSONAL INFORMATION COLLECTED

As is typical with online commerce web sites, we collect information directly from you. Examples of this type of information include, but are not limited to: name, address, telephone number, email address, credit card number, purchase and ordering information, demographical information, and sizing information.

This information may be collected at various places throughout our web site such as completing your order, contacting our customer service through our online contact form, email newsletter subscription, contests, or subscribing to other special offers and programs.

## INFORMATION COLLECTED INDIRECTLY

When you visit FrightCatalog.com, we collect technical information such as the web browser you are using and its version, service provider information, IP address, and the web site from which you came (Google.com, Bing.com, etc.). This information is typically anonymous in the sense that it does not contain any of your personal information, such as your name, address, email address, or telephone number. However, at times, we may associate this technical information with your personal information if you provide it.

To better understand how you use our web site, we use a browser feature known as a cookie. A cookie is a small data file that is stored by your web browser on your computer. It is used to do things like see how you navigate our web site, and remember you and your online purchases when you return. This helps us to improve our web site, provide better customer service, personalize your online experience, and personalize offers to you based on your unique purchase history.

## LIMITING INFORMATION WE CAN USE

There are steps you can take to limit the information that we collect and use. If at any time you have questions about your personal information and how it is collected, please email our customer service department at [service@frightcatalog.com](mailto:service@frightcatalog.com) or fill our online contact form.

If you would like to stop the future delivery of our email offers, simply follow the removal instructions located at the bottom of every email message or complete our online unsubscribe form. This will stop any email offers from us; however, we may still contact you via email for operation or transactional messages such as order confirmations or customer service communications. We also may occasionally provide you with the opportunity to opt back in to our email offers.

If you would like to prevent us from collecting technical information from you, you may turn off cookies or clear your cookies from your web browser. Follow the instructions provided by the web browser’s developer to do this. Please note that by doing this, not all cookies may be blocked and some information may be transferred to us.

## UPDATING MY INFORMATION

If you would like to update your personal information with us, you may modify your information by logging into your FrightCatalog.com account. You may also modify your information by contacting our customer service department.

## HOW IS YOUR INFORMATION SECURED?

FrightCatalog.com has the following types of security measures: limited access data-centers, firewall technology, and secure-socket-layer (SSL) certificate authentication. SSL is encryption technology that provides security for information that is transmitted over the Internet. This site will only accept an order from a web browser that supports communication through SSL technology.

## WILL WE SHARE YOUR INFORMATION?

FrightCatalog.com takes the security of your personal information very seriously. At no time will FrightCatalog.com share personal information you have provided to us with any 3rd party. This information includes the following:

  * Your Name
  * Address
  * Email Address
  * Telephone Number
  * Credit / Debit Card Information

Information collected indirectly through technology such as web browser cookies may be shared with 3rd party sites and companies to help us improve our web site. This information is kept confidential as well, however, if you have any questions regarding how this information is shared, please contact our customer service department.
